It's not gonna be one number.
Oh, God, that's lazy writing.
I still got it.
Put that back in
your prison wallet.
I don't know how to thank you.
But I do know how to hug you.
No.Yes.
Here we go. Bring it in.
Come on.
Pelvis to pelvis.
Let's go tip to tip.
There we go. The kids
call this docking.
Is there a knife in my dick?
There's a knife in your dick.
I'm just gonna back up now.
Yeah, yeah. No need
to go full Yentl.
Gonna pretend like
that never happened.
Let's go home, Russell.
All you dirty mutants
are gonna rot in
hell with the boy!
Your souls are
beyond redemption!
Let's see your soul, perv!
No, no! No! No more!
We're better than that!
We're better than him!
No more senseless violence!
No more bloodshed!
We'll let karma
take care of him.
The day of reckoning is here!
I'm gonna miss him.
He seemed great.
Whoo!
Courage, motherfuckers!
And karma, motherfucker.
I could hear you coming
the last 30 seconds.
I could barely keep
a straight face.
I want some more.
I bet you do, Brown Panther.
We should leave before
Fuckernaut wakes up.
Good call. You guys
coming with us?
No, we'll get the kids
back to the mansion.
Besides, we're X-Men.
No, you're X-People.
You're exhausting.
I see what you did there. Puns.
Our door's always open.
That's kind, but I'm not
ready to date again.
Let alone two women.
God, you're a douche.
Bye, Wade! Bye, Yukio!
What do you get
when you take eight
feet of chrome...
one pinch of courage...
a cup of good luck...
a dab of racism...
a splash of diabetes...
and a wheelbarrow full
of stage four cancer?
Answer: a family.
See? I didn't lie what
kind of film this was.
If there's anything you
take away today...
other than the need to Google,
"What the fuck is dubstep?"...
it's that we all need
to belong to someone.
How something so small generates
enough energy to
reverse time is...
Oh, just fix it, Eleven,
or I'll take it to
the Genius Bar.
Cable's gonna kill you
when he finds out.
Never heard of him.
Why do you think
I'm helping him?
The Lord works in
mysterious ways,
don't I? A good day.
Bye, Wade!
Bye, Yukio!
That was probably a bad idea.
What have we done?
I hope we sharpened the
cream cheese spreader.
I'll be right back!
We're definitely
naming our kid Cher!
Whoo!
Peter!
Whoo! X-Force!
Walk away! Just walk away!
But we're X-Force!
Nope! We're not.
X-Force is just a marketing tool
designed by Fox executives...
to keep Josh Brolin employed.
It doesn't exist.
All right, well, this
has been pretty scary!
And I need to feed my cat!
Go home, Sugarbear. Go home.
Okay. Will you give
Domino my email?
Wade, is that you?
I guess Stryker finally
figured out how to shut you up.
Hey! It's me! Don't scratch!
Just cleaning up the timelines!
Look, eventually you're going
to hang up the claws...
and it's gonna make a
lot of people very sad.
Huh?
But one day, your old pal
Wade's gonna ask you...
to get back in the saddle again.
And when he does, say yes.
Oh, right.
Love you!
Goddamn, that's beautiful.
You're welcome, Canada.
Boy howdy.
Hi. This is a toughie.
Yeesh.
Oh, yes. You're already
practicing your salute, huh?
Yes, you are. Well, we'll
take care of that, won't we?
Jesus Christ! This is so
much harder than I thought.
Oh, I'm going to hell.
That makes two of us.
You can do this.
This is crazy. This is crazy.
All right.
Maximum effort.
That's okay. Let me see here.
Oh, God.
That's why you're such
a little bastard.
No one's ever changed you.
Yeah, you got a big, old
stinky in there, don't you?
God, it smells like
Hitler's anus...
which would makes sense,
wouldn't it? Yeah.
I think we both know
I don't have what it
takes to do this...
so I'm just gonna change
your diaper real quick...
and then I'm gonna come
back with my friend, Cable.
He loves killing kids.